<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kim&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kim&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:23:42 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Model Context Protocol (and some learning reflections along the way)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:23:42 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mcp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;reflections&#34;&gt;Reflections&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past few weeks have been a very interesting learning curve for me, trying to dive deeper into the Agentic AI world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I signed up for the Huggingface AI Agent Course from the beginning, super excited to get a grip on what was announced to be the greatest trend in 2025, to learn how to create my own agents, and to uncover the RAG hype around it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember being so excited learning weekly, waiting for the weekly course release and complete the assignments, as if I&amp;rsquo;m in school again. And in the end, I did managed to create a general AI assistant and evaluated it on a proper AI benchmark for its capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding LLM and AI Agents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/agentllm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 07:33:53 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/agentllm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent statements, NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang declared that we are entering the era of “agentic AI” - a new generation of AI that can autonomously perform complex, multi-step tasks such as data analysis, decision-making, or even interacting with both digital and physical environments. These AI agents will not stop at being software tools only but are now envisioned to be a new digital workforce that will soon revolutionize industries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
